{
    "deck": null,
    "cards": [
        {
            "id": 1560696532662,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "heir",
            "answer": "heredera\nheredero",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.413Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.413Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 630716048145,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sinful",
            "answer": "pecaminosa\npecaminoso",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.414Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.414Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1633074260790,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "leisure",
            "answer": "ocio",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.415Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.415Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1554069248439,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "Ubiquitous",
            "answer": "Ubicua\nUbicuo",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.415Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.415Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 461732910980,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "hierarchies",
            "answer": "jerarquías",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.416Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.416Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1085419476881,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "Bounded",
            "answer": "Encerrada\nEncerrado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.417Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.417Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 821097015852,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "seldom",
            "answer": "raramente",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.419Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.419Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 163106752457,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "naysayer",
            "answer": "detractora\ndetractor",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.420Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.420Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 39901599185,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "succinctly",
            "answer": "sucintamente",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.421Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.421Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1483899938403,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "deprecated",
            "answer": "obsoleta\nobsoleto",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.421Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.421Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 842611590213,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "Reliability",
            "answer": "Fiabilidad",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.422Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.422Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 55649321757,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "stagnating",
            "answer": "estancado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.422Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.422Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1591910699762,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "wardrobe",
            "answer": "guardarropa",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.425Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.425Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 57741421853,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "conversely",
            "answer": "Por el contrario",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.426Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.426Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1246310496574,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "assignment",
            "answer": "asignación",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.427Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.427Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 307430757980,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "whim",
            "answer": "capricho",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.427Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.427Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 35069598610,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "eager",
            "answer": "ansiosa\nansioso",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.428Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.428Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 424341230945,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "entangled",
            "answer": "enredada\nenredado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.429Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.429Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 245069152082,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "hence",
            "answer": "por lo tanto",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.430Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.430Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 554081924074,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "deceit",
            "answer": "engaño",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.431Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.431Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 166001203137,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "framed",
            "answer": "enmarcada\nenmarcado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.431Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.431Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 506873850018,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "icicles",
            "answer": "carámbanos",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.432Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.432Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 992446465083,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "twirl",
            "answer": "giro",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.433Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.433Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1559196074794,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "fragged",
            "answer": "fragmentada\nfragmentado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.435Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.435Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 169626139719,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "hardwired",
            "answer": "cableado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.437Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.437Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 681701321796,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "bungled",
            "answer": "torpe",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.438Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.438Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1327365516440,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "heft",
            "answer": "peso",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.438Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.438Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 485730665207,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "quell",
            "answer": "calmar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.439Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.439Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 282520556294,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "grudging",
            "answer": "avara\navaro",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.440Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.440Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 141270531094,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "pity",
            "answer": "lástima",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.441Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.441Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 60185364456,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sweeping",
            "answer": "barrido",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.442Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.442Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 653363446510,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "wisely",
            "answer": "sabiamente",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.443Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.443Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 213854130359,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "rejoice",
            "answer": "alegrarse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.444Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.444Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 391720591883,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "rattled",
            "answer": "traqueteado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.445Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.445Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1450531051005,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "spares",
            "answer": "repuestas\nrepuestos",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.446Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.446Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 253762428981,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "spelunking",
            "answer": "espeleología",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.447Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.447Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1171278861160,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "supper",
            "answer": "cena",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.447Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.447Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 33995667313,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "overall",
            "answer": "en general",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.448Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.448Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 277996151857,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "heartwarming",
            "answer": "reconfortante",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.449Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.449Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1551183303164,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "owe",
            "answer": "deber",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.451Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.451Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 781594850214,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "depth",
            "answer": "profundidad",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.452Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.452Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 401127754845,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "Audit",
            "answer": "Auditoría",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.454Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.454Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 911333676441,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "back off",
            "answer": "Apártate",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.455Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.455Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1094345108655,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "move along",
            "answer": "superar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.456Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.456Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 612902134646,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sideshow",
            "answer": "atracción secundaria",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.458Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.458Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 345672985435,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "deceptions",
            "answer": "engaños",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.459Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.459Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 294130454348,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "brag",
            "answer": "jactarse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.460Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.460Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1488195948377,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "caveat",
            "answer": "advertencia",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.461Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.461Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1124101810232,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "get by",
            "answer": "arreglárselas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.463Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.463Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 750153588505,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "cheers on",
            "answer": "anima",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.464Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.464Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 91272790831,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "grumpy",
            "answer": "gruñona\ngruñón",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.465Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.465Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1051255722802,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "harsh",
            "answer": "dura\nduro",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.467Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.467Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 244922847336,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "tasty",
            "answer": "sabrosa\nsabroso",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.468Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.468Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 592917469183,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "upset",
            "answer": "trastornada\ntrastornado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.470Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.470Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 442008494555,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "shrewdest",
            "answer": "más astuto",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.472Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.472Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1495141632635,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "lossless",
            "answer": "sin pérdidas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.473Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.473Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 845384356726,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "narrow",
            "answer": "estrecho",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.475Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.475Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1553712695525,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "put up",
            "answer": "Hospedarse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.476Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.476Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 251931617267,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "starred",
            "answer": "sembrado de estrellas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.478Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.478Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 926317893412,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "lash out",
            "answer": "arremeter",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.479Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.479Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1388987852358,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "pipe up",
            "answer": "empezar a hablar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.481Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.481Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 612662385244,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "neighborhoods",
            "answer": "barrios",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.482Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.482Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1095046413876,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "attendance",
            "answer": "asistencia",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.484Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.484Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 423436362389,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "called out",
            "answer": "gritó",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.485Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.485Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 287646288999,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "carpet",
            "answer": "alfombra",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.487Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.487Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1215034294382,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "drapes",
            "answer": "cortinas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.489Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.489Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1279378170629,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "rave",
            "answer": "delirio",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.491Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.491Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 950388714013,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "withdraw",
            "answer": "retirar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.493Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.493Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 273618464827,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "bluffing",
            "answer": "faroleando",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.495Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.495Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1620970487119,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "tempt",
            "answer": "tentar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.496Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.496Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1344583924656,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "slowing down",
            "answer": "Ralentizando",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.498Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.498Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 707328100582,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "deploy",
            "answer": "desplegar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.500Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.500Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 813959473961,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "kneel",
            "answer": "arrodillarse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.502Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.502Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 588246439049,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "blow up",
            "answer": "explotar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.504Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.504Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 300374410785,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "band aid",
            "answer": "Tirita",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.506Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.506Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 572209671106,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "backyard",
            "answer": "patio interior",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.508Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.508Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 155625649957,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "approval",
            "answer": "aprobación",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.510Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.510Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1438131636035,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "felony",
            "answer": "delito",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.512Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.512Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1583082427195,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "widower",
            "answer": "viudo",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.514Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.514Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1512544911954,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "tight",
            "answer": "apretada\napretado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.517Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.517Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 376353312268,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "doomed",
            "answer": "condenada\ncondenado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.521Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.521Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 779165768192,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "narrows",
            "answer": "se estrecha",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.523Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.523Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1224449436062,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "passed out",
            "answer": "Desmayado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.525Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.525Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1190733600454,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "owes",
            "answer": "debe",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.527Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.527Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1456922537208,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "doubt",
            "answer": "duda",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.530Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.530Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1363082397811,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "warrant",
            "answer": "orden",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.533Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.533Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1019393623053,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "poisoned",
            "answer": "envenenado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.535Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.535Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 171009986314,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sinner",
            "answer": "pecadora\npecador",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.538Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.538Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1320445272249,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "awakening",
            "answer": "despertar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.540Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.540Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1290808248389,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sharp",
            "answer": "aguda\nagudo",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.542Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.542Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 82175932394,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "shake",
            "answer": "sacudir",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.545Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.545Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 79572399362,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "enlightment",
            "answer": "ilustración",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.547Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.547Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1521995668831,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "scratching",
            "answer": "rascarse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.549Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.549Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 458114098042,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "ropes",
            "answer": "cuerdas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.552Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.552Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 409591802987,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "swish",
            "answer": "silbido",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.555Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.555Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 138787265618,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sensitive",
            "answer": "sensible",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.558Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.558Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 244654972719,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sigh",
            "answer": "suspiro",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.561Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.561Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1113274993293,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "tricky",
            "answer": "difícil",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.563Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.563Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1396568941480,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "shouts",
            "answer": "gritos",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.566Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.566Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 964299565035,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "indoor",
            "answer": "interior",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.568Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.568Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 637045849154,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "success",
            "answer": "éxito",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.571Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.571Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 848286026467,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "perks",
            "answer": "ventajas",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.574Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.574Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 867137662238,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sully",
            "answer": "manchar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.576Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.576Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1508614635507,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "illness",
            "answer": "enfermedad",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.579Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.579Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 542326203346,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "claws",
            "answer": "garras",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.581Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.581Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1271191861062,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "wind",
            "answer": "viento",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.584Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.584Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 636071126573,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "pull over",
            "answer": "volcar",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.586Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.586Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 622321196137,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "sword",
            "answer": "espada",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.589Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.589Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 119789598968,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "grizzly",
            "answer": "oso pardo",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.591Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.591Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 821528150951,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "twigs",
            "answer": "leña menuda",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.594Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.594Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 624739797588,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "whack",
            "answer": "golpear",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.596Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.596Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1630301776524,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "vow",
            "answer": "voto",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.598Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.598Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 377084906074,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "framed",
            "answer": "enmarcado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.600Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.600Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 172105581617,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "along",
            "answer": "a lo largo",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.602Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.602Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1531163866539,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "fond of",
            "answer": "aficionado a",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.605Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.605Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 321820918060,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "digging",
            "answer": "excavación",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.607Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.607Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 354805384404,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "bolsters",
            "answer": "refuerza",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.609Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.609Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1379362968521,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "engaged",
            "answer": "comprometida\ncomprometido",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.612Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.612Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 290623898620,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "squealed",
            "answer": "chillido",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.614Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.614Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 524316807781,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "picky",
            "answer": "difícil",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.616Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.616Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1223596498571,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "butcher",
            "answer": "carnicera\ncarnicero",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.618Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.618Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 540290623638,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "tricked",
            "answer": "bureado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.620Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.620Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 890276166036,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "shitty",
            "answer": "de mierda",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.623Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.623Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1395144282283,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "speakeasy",
            "answer": "hablado",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.626Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.626Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 1227850778717,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "fend",
            "answer": "defenderse",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.628Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.628Z"
        },
        {
            "id": 893109425746,
            "deck_id": 474317325266,
            "question": "duly",
            "answer": "debidamente",
            "repetitions": 0,
            "ease_factor": 2.5,
            "interval": 0,
            "review_date": null,
            "review_date_human": "Has never been reviewed",
            "created_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.631Z",
            "updated_at": "2021-10-18T18:00:36.631Z"
        }
    ],
    "cardsDisplayed": [],
    "meta": null
}